<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>It&#39;s Nothing</title>
    <link>https://www.itsnothing.de/</link>
    <description>Recent content on It&#39;s Nothing</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.itsnothing.de/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Portfolio updated</title>
      <link>https://www.itsnothing.de/post/july-22-update-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.itsnothing.de/post/july-22-update-2/</guid>
      <description>Took the time to update the portfolio page to include some preview images/animations to showcase more of the projects I have been working on in the past years. Check it out, it is linked in the bar above ;)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>July 22 Update</title>
      <link>https://www.itsnothing.de/post/july-22-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.itsnothing.de/post/july-22-update/</guid>
      <description>Another update! Since we could not secure funding for further projects with Gentleforge I am currently looking for work again. Great opportunity to update the portfolio/website here.
I already updated the &amp;ldquo;Stuff I built&amp;rdquo; page with some new details and am going to write an update on what I am doing on the side at the moment next.
In the last few months I started playing around with Yahaha, a software platform for creating real-time 3D content.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>February 22 Update</title>
      <link>https://www.itsnothing.de/post/february-22-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.itsnothing.de/post/february-22-update/</guid>
      <description>Oh, hey, the first update in checks notes years. I am currently working on a project with some motion controls, if it works out I will write a post about it.
Here is a sneak peak using the Nuitrack SDK to get some live skeleton data in Unity:
 Your browser does not support video.  Since the last update I started working at https://www.gentleforge.com/ and updated the page info accordingly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting old unity projects - Part 2</title>
      <link>https://www.itsnothing.de/post/revisiting-old-unity-projects-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.itsnothing.de/post/revisiting-old-unity-projects-part-2/</guid>
      <description>Last time I revisited Potion Shift from April 2016 to make a 64-bit-version for Android. That went pretty well, so this time I&amp;rsquo;ll go back to the first jam game I did. It is called Affectionate Armament, made for Ludum Dare 32 with the theme &amp;ldquo;An Unconventional Weapon&amp;rdquo;. The idea we went with was to have a weapon with feelings. It&amp;rsquo;s a two player action game with one weapon, and once a player grabs it they can start shooting the other player.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting old unity projects</title>
      <link>https://www.itsnothing.de/post/revisiting-old-unity-projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.itsnothing.de/post/revisiting-old-unity-projects/</guid>
      <description>I have a bunch of old Unity projects lying around, mostly from gamejams. Instant learning, just looking at the menu for our 2016 Ludum Dare Game &amp;ldquo;Potion Shift&amp;rdquo;: Don&amp;rsquo;t be too ambitious with announcing features/content, especially don&amp;rsquo;t put them in your main menu:
Coming, Coming Soon&amp;hellip; I don&amp;rsquo;t think so :P
From now on I&amp;rsquo;ll just put things in blogposts that I can silently delete later to undo any unfulfilled announcements ;)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating websites with hugo</title>
      <link>https://www.itsnothing.de/post/creating-websites-with-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.itsnothing.de/post/creating-websites-with-hugo/</guid>
      <description>For the longest time, I used to build websites with Wordpress. It&amp;rsquo;s easy, performance was never that much of an issue for me and it enabled me to give non-technical users the opportunity to create content. But if you ever had a wordpress blog with a handful of plugins running unattended for a while you know that, well you can&amp;rsquo;t leave it unattended actually. Even though wordpress has an automatic updating mechanism by now, keeping up interoperability of plugins/theme and the base wordpress install requires attention from time to time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More Info added</title>
      <link>https://www.itsnothing.de/post/moar-info/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.itsnothing.de/post/moar-info/</guid>
      <description>I updated the about me and added a small showcase with information about what I did.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://www.itsnothing.de/about-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.itsnothing.de/about-me/</guid>
      <description>Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m Ekki! I like to make and play games, build software and talking for hours about infrastructure.
I am currently looking for work as a game developer (design and or programming), preferably in an indie team.
You can find more info on what I did professionally on the Portfolio page.
For CV info please refer to my LinkedIn-Profile.
Various other interests? Check Twitter</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About This Site</title>
      <link>https://www.itsnothing.de/about-this-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.itsnothing.de/about-this-site/</guid>
      <description>How is this site made? The page is built with Hugo, I have already written about it here.
The theme is called terminal and it is made by panr.
You can retrace all the customizations I made and will make on the blog&amp;rsquo;s GitHub repository.
What about those neat graphics? The images are virtuosly made with Microsoft Paint, with the help of a graphics tablet or directly on a touchscreen, so you&amp;rsquo;ll only find hand-made, artisanal blog graphics here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello Visitor</title>
      <link>https://www.itsnothing.de/post/hello/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.itsnothing.de/post/hello/</guid>
      <description>Hey, it&amp;rsquo;s a blog again. This is where it all starts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Portfolio</title>
      <link>https://www.itsnothing.de/portfolio/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.itsnothing.de/portfolio/</guid>
      <description>I like to build things! This page shows some of the things I helped to build. For a CV-like overview visit my LinkedIn-page.
What I like most is the practical aspect of building (virtual) things: writing code, creating prototypes, taking an idea into the real world and then seeing what works and - behold - what does not work as intended. But since I always worked in small teams that require a large amount of self-organization I am used to spending just as much as time with the theoretical side of it: working on game design and technical architectures and figuring out how to make something that is fun to interact with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Impressum</title>
      <link>https://www.itsnothing.de/impressum/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.itsnothing.de/impressum/</guid>
      <description>Impressum Jan-Erik Baehr Blombachweg 8a 40625 Duesseldorf E-Mail: admin@itsnothing.de
Verantwortlich für den Inhalt (gem. § 55 Abs. 2 RStV): Jan-Erik Bähr Blombachweg 8a 40625 Düsseldorf
How is this made? Made with Hugo
Theme made by panr</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.itsnothing.de/imprint/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.itsnothing.de/imprint/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
